{
    "id": "d10c0e40756645278bc8d59aae2e7f90",
    "title": "See, look and watch exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "04c4ca6ab0de4862a09af99e8e49e58f",
            "title": "See, Look And Watch",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Ring up and .................................. whether she is at home.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "see",
                        "look",
                        "watch"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ....................................... a dark figure behind the window.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "saw",
                        "watched",
                        "looked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Suddenly I ........................................ something strange.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "saw",
                        "watched",
                        "looked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Please ........................................ at this photo.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "watch",
                        "see",
                        "look"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Do you ........................................ that man in the blue shirt?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "see",
                        "watch",
                        "look"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "..................................... what you have done.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "See",
                        "Watch",
                        "Look"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I like to ..................................... football matches on TV.",
                    "description": "Either see or watch is possible here.",
                    "answers": [
                        "see",
                        "watch",
                        "look"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "That kid spends too much time .................................. TV.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "seeing",
                        "watching",
                        "looking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Iâ€™m looking to ................................. whether there is any food left.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "see",
                        "look",
                        "watch"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I .................................... they are going to put up taxes again.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "look",
                        "see",
                        "watch"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}